{
    "results": [{
            "id": 1,
            "question": "Who is Darth Varder in the popular movie Star Wars",
            "correct_answer": "Anakin Skywalker",
            "incorrect_answer": [
                "Obi Wan Kenobi", "Master Yoda", "Palpatine"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "In the movie The Matrix, what color of pill does Neo take?",
            "correct_answer": "red",
            "incorrect_answer": [
                "blue", "green", "black"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What's the name of Simba's nasty uncle?",
            "correct_answer": "Scar",
            "incorrect_answer": [
                "Jafar", "Gaston", "Shere Khan"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "How many Jumanji films have been made so far?",
            "correct_answer": "4",
            "incorrect_answer": [
                "7", "3", "2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "In the movie Doctor Strange: Multiverse of Madness, who was the major villain",
            "correct_answer": "Wanda",
            "incorrect_answer": [
                "Bulky", "Spiderman", "Agatha"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Which American movie studio introduced sound films?",
            "correct_answer": "Warner Brothers",
            "incorrect_answer": [
                "Columbia Pictures", "20th Century Fox", "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "To which year does Marty McFly travel back in time, in Back to the Future?",
            "correct_answer": "1955",
            "incorrect_answer": [
                "1919", "1976", "1984"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Who is Superman's biological father?",
            "correct_answer": "Jor-el",
            "incorrect_answer": [
                "Jonathan", "Homelander", "Bro-el"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "Pick the odd hero not part of the Justice League",
            "correct_answer": "Moon Knight",
            "incorrect_answer": [
                "Batman", "Green Lantern", "Superman"
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "Who said this, 'YOU SHALL NOT PASS' ?",
            "correct_answer": "Gandalf",
            "incorrect_answer": [
                "Merlin", "Yoda", "Dumbledore"
            ]
        }
    ]
}